hi welcome back to the wheel of life at
home retreat hi slammer Tatanka melody
rotary to punt retreat Daruma and I'd
like to thank standing again for transit
thanks for staying in America
interesting 10 staying in Potomac Rasika
but as deadly lucky seeing that the jail
is a jail get that istituto Prasad to
young Lisa put melihat bow up injera
added up injera
in the pictures is a jail then Camarena
a Taliban Chara we actually we used to
have a very active program of teaching
la même in the jail kita Spinelli Tulum
America programs are active and open a
column rim dip injera and it helped the
prisoners a lot and the government
thanked us because the prisoners got
less fights tentative annette momento
para de Hanan 10 member in tibet Rima
kazakh parikamma karna para tener la
pista Capri claw he
and the picture you see here is kind of
perfect for a jail because it's it's
really depressing in a Jew Romario and
early at escena de la serda spend era
yangsun pune karna banal Bannerman a
deacon depend Jarrah
so when we study the wheel of China
wheel of life in the monastery
Terracotta kakoton periodically - Pandy
pyaara we study it from a set of books
called so cool
coming blood Jerry Nadler is a to set
book we only support circle and it's a
tradition to take about five different
subjects desiderata TC paluska Tali
Mamata player and young rápida and you
squeeze special subjects out of bigger
books like the way you would squeeze
medicine out of an herb
Tyrande Masuka Mata platter on Kyushu
starry Paku Paku en la b bastarz
apartheid era and obamas apart ariram
Wan Jia mo
and for a computer project saving the
ancient books tanto pro yet computer
kita when yellamma can buku buku no that
was the actually the first book we ever
printed was called circled after five
books that are extracted from the big
box it is Piniella cuckoo pertama young
/ nakamichi attack this a boots of coal
NEMA beaucoup Youngjae embroidery pukka
pukka pasar
and you'll be interested to know that
the whole wheel of life teaching as it's
taught in the monastery and we study it
for about two three months
it all comes from one line from my trip
I should say one verse not one
and I think you've heard me say this
line before
Dennison game damn game Payton's an
onion good night engine down jean-luc
tuna look turn down little topper J
that's it
it teaches both of my instilled in him
and neither can katoa
paddy a man's life done Rohtak a two
part and the part that I want to talk
about today is the ending part it says
Tanjung Belgium look Tintin look me to
look to look meetin look 10 beginning in
Cyprus that I can hurry in a turnip
again a chaotic attack one sugars to to
to the streets looked on Pratt Lisa -
mommy - - aah - aah mommy - teka teka
mamita poor precocity Tomoko no papa
yeah Patriota saya teddy mm oh my G
Volodya Pretoria that's looped enemies
normal order look Tony - ferati Ruta
normal look meetin which is sometimes
called mundo la loo look me - and young
gotta get a discipline no dice - turn
the wheel backwards yam pratima Muhtar
Poli
to shut down the wheel dock my Hindi
Kannada so you know you kind of think
must be since it says backwards JD and
dyspnea propagate it's our stay put gel
and thirty-two up Alaska's Alaska so
turned on but optimist I am i real oh no
semi trigger unless idolized by God
Camus 10 comma Sam did you come oh then
I armed the Karma come again Simon
percent I mean you could have some
strange ideas like Messiah and Abba zaba
Maliki Papa et a nice Appetit but here
in the lamrim decks they describe what
it really means to turn the wheel around
the PTC needle Amram recommend American
APIs paneer Tina Mamata Rhoda
did a little dr. Koch MIT alum chic
NIAMS and lenders were following the
Tibetan apart which will enable you to
stop the wheel of life by reversing it
Chiquita Maggie capacity petaca Andaman
Gambia challenging economy mooking can
under on top of the control dependent
into reversal of life to shut down the
Jerry Appa Atheneum Impala Kodaka to
Panama can thicken not agreed upon
merica kappa merica got paid you check
on if you start misunderstanding then
you start making common chica and mi
gente con castle Appa Herman maka anger
but honey man when you do the kitchen
mata ki time I'm going which is where
you should take all your time and but
under Horace Mombasa more that manda if
you can't take it to the kitchen it's
not Dumber vikarna tidak bisa man bagna
cauda pour into poo can Darma okay and
what if it is terminated
okay then I PI CK to Dharma makanda Aras
be some ammonia cat approves the salsa
party there shouldn't be anything in the
300,000 books of Buddhism that we have
that you cannot find in the kitchen
sorry aunty Dada sat upon dorita kuratas
rip okuu policeman
Yankee family Chianti revisited mo conde
topper
and if something good or bad is
happening in the kitchen it must be
described in the ancient books Santa
Casa SWAT a young by Attleboro digty
teed up or Ito pasta de la scandal on
poco boku-kun Oh
because the ancient books were written
for the kid an apple could do not eat
Ulis untucked up or soma liquid got
Marik but got a detain got my if she
can't stop having misunderstanding about
her husband young Bharati chica Pia
because she doesn't say dick a deity
that magnetic incited a Dallas monopod
but I say I know Debra I said I wanna
put that aside and examine cool ah no
she just reversed the first link yeah hi
naming Ambala Cantt and she just blocked
the first thing yeah
but among Holland thought if you block
that I didn't do anything
chicken diamond collar set it up knock
on a path and automatically you will not
reach the second link commodious is an
automatic and a Teta a comment a Python
katoa I'm not ready to put under poteau
ok good second link will never come
tomorrow
Jada Pinkett Roger Akita man at the
Kentucky don't forget Wheel of Life is a
kind of a bad it's a Miss named Miss
nomer
John aloo paratha coupon at al-assad SWA
to namie amuro namie inshallah
it's not really the real fire-eater
Buchan Pinar Pinero de dooda also has
life Messiah who tries to communicate a
dancer the wheel of badly painful knife
in a bra tiro de quito pinion guru then
coupon yang Manya catkin so he says but
it's toppling to see karma Kanda Kanda
normal Sato and Amanda cantata no matter
what and eventually you'll stop
everything up to getting old and dying
but a kid yeah I'm not gonna get the
cancer monument JD do I dance a cara de
Mille time shaking Samaras a socket lmp2
panda I can't help it also don't think
we love life means if you get out of the
wheel of life you have to die or
disappear
Jukka jongmin / Picaro ducky Dupin
bratty seeker and a quarter I wrote a
key to / and Harris Matty
otama Gila in the Wheel of Life for
example in the painting that ironically
Dupin me Sonya Tom Wilkinson the Buddha
is outside of you sang Buddha Prada de
la rata and he's pointing to the moon
and I am annoying to Coppola which
represents me mother yeah Milwaukee
linear Ivana okay let's go back to the
text
lay down your Montandon young contender
Cindy did they don't do that means let's
let's kind of summarize everything dot
do not America tamarin cusamano you can
take all 12 links and I Department
number is more to a blast out done and
just for summary we can divide them
differently than many ways than Honduran
gossin ketupat member kiemce rica tengan
Limpy panicked Arab rápida Theresa
Rokita mom became America's Apollonia we
can divide them into number one Commerce
get that up at member kiemce but I
committed a number satu no got a
negative sense
no what do I pick era negative and
number three pain number three okay and
a tap on member kimmykak path tongue SEP
separation among but if I cancel and
Buster you negative emotions
dick Atari Talton adalah MOC negative
that's a misunderstanding your husband
in Turkish Alabama native so me I'm
super we've been saying like negative
coffee meditation are you sorry you has
been no thank you John Sapien kita taka
taka semantics of emeritus indicative
then Lamba is like advanced negative
coffee meditation then Cambodian Lempa
submitted a Pattaya at the Opel antara
but react but Anakin oxide and Swami
saya young but the react by design so
those three are all negative thoughts
dedicate a guide to samanya adapt akira
nakano does if I turn out I know more to
add an autonomous to our karma do I do I
got my got different stages of karma
Pepita up-and-coming verbatim to is what
do I tell her yeah like a watermelon
[Music]
yes Appetit America that no more spool
ooh
yeah c'mom attack beep it Camus concea
yeah Baku steady atomically to swat Oh
Simon on copy saya
then he says a strange thing so I'm
adding dunya and the other seven they're
suffering and a clock module jr. then to
chill Anya records loop then comedian
deep blue drop Aryan Aryan and this
happens to be the same text about the
essence of dependent origination that we
had before it's very short it's like one
or two pages
Danine Adela texting somewhat Anton in T
sorry director condom and our en kita
disco sequence promised an appendix
Hannes Otto Otto do a Holloman
so let's follow the Tibetan because
there's gonna be two to interesting
points here did America's I could be
positive it cannot can added to a point
minority see me Dumbo gap a good no more
one and and the ninth
I negative first the first one's a lot
bigger negative you see thomaskelep and
some villain and le haut de pétanque
assemble on the garden yeah magnet and
symbol on Laguna
why didn't he say 9/3 and he just said
nein
la Petite ever gotten Zombieland and
Iranian monitor Kinsella poetry and he
didn't have room to put through like to
proceed and yet it up when you're on the
bank Attica
so don't get confused he's gonna bingo
you city you should hear a poopa another
spending a BA coupon now it's clear
number one number one number eight
number nine these two are negative
emotions
Misato no but still abundant number
symbol and number two and number ten
these are the two Karma's
these two are Kremers no but now the
rest seventh and remaining seven scarin
to choose assign decide dunya okay I'd
like to go to the original text scanning
sale are looking in massive text me any
time this is a mixed nuts rule subtypes
Antonella after on mixed nuts anytime
there's a quotation in a bird so Deb
Korea Dakota pendulum beaucoup the rule
of our mixed nuts translation team Turin
dimpled chin ma mixed nuts we are all
reincarnation of the students of master
Schwinn son in the wild goose pagoda
tower during the Tonto give aspirin
cannot see dairy more it master swan
song the wild goose pagoda Manara lama
dynasty tongue go check it and make sure
it's correct
Sagarika tip on Porky Pig sad and pasta
candy to Panera
so I checked it it is a memory Sonya and
then I said to myself it's correct dan
saya
Alice Emily had an asset oka tamae beta
the way it's coded in the Lamia
diradical deeply loved him
the last line says shock module name
means now the last the remaining
where is the racket muhammadun e pratt
Escarra and terakhir - Julius Caesar
recommend Rita that's a little
uncomfortable right I mean others must
be suffering also the whole wheel is
suffering Pepito stickety Danny a man
can also see a young lion passage'
commander Rita's lauraaradi - manda Rita
the real ancient
tenure version of dispersed firstly I
had any detangler Kuno
it says slob but then young not me okay
who can be ready city Martin young young
Bharati to Joo young Teresa Adela chica
I think listen to this class so far the
discipleship oppinion bananer can
cluster Joey me I can accept that
three three of those are negative
emotions one Cyberman dramatical de
españa dela MOC negative numbers are -
nobody droppin done no mas and villain I
can understand that two of them are
karma number ten number ten it is among
at the power to add that is monumental
and the remaining cellular surfers the
picking up on appeal on then to
chu-young those first five show yourself
an app idea below but keep the canopic
and Kellie Meyer but I might you come
underneath that and if you thought that
when you heard me say it first then jika
end up at a picket park Attica
undemanding I'd say incorrect not a
cognate le Badal because versus the
remaining seven are also suffering can
is a banana magnetic and to jooheon vs.
a chukerman dorita so I made some my
very 3rd grade child like drawings here
the same improper camber an iconoclastic
acai Odyssey knee
I put some color around the first eighth
and the ninth links which are negative
emotions tamata camba prep awareness
guitar taught on yang pertama cattle
upon danke symbol annyeong a derivative
the mood and camera around to intend
together Sam I got the proper wanna ski
that toward and I put colors around 3 to
7 and 11 to 12 this is 7 then kumuda and
LM camera bruh goodness I'm gonna
wanna ski that it doesn't pay to 2 times
a plus k tu hablas by now you know that
these two groups are kind of the same
thing then the two suggests Karen and at
our power catwalk Lompoc in the
adolescent is yang sama three four five
six seven D camp at Lima Namjoo every
throw that's bluster or less like a
habit sama cannot betray my mind comes
into my mind
papica p karin-sama super Saiya link for
my body and mind are inside my mind
about that but to Putin picker and say a
prayer that he terrified my eyes and
ears and nose etcetera grow inside me
mama tattling I did he do then the light
to booty Ptolemy Pooh sire link six they
make contact with the outside world
America Moroccan contacting Antonia you
are link seven because of that contact I
get feelings like good feelings are
feelings tanto Gioconda Kentucky to say
I'm Anna Paquin presence uppity present
bike four five six
he kept America samosa but is a blaster
together are one whole human life so
blessed and wobbler for samma
sambuddhassa to surah manusia I'm born I
get old and I say like him did he do wow
that's a man did succumb tumbled come so
those are the three images I put up this
it can dump oh did he toured a lot Iike
combo good long done
he said interesting you can think of the
first line of the verse okay
Deb Takata Minari and at the Putnam
beacon but his parameter is our Genesis
the first and eighth and the ninth these
are the negative emotions Tunica intima
Danielson a mental process of motivation
to do something bad and I miss my Ganga
is a burger process but if I see you end
up Malacca Kansas were too young Peru
then you can think of the next verse
it's next line commodians number two
number ten Arcana paris obliquity a
magnetic anomaly to add a number subpool
Adela karma if you think about it
chicken Epicure Bertolini and number 10
number to order numbers Apollo these are
karma expressed by doing things or
saying things in Adela karma and eaten a
banana koukin ha ha ha
Ottoman Otakon ha ha
where's the mental comer demonic are
memento he already covered
Yasuda Montano Pina the club professor
Klump Oporto three mental afflictions
are Armand katika pandita and mental a
Dalek are momenta
which means link number 1 is negative
young BRT taught anomer Sato at a lotta
number 2 number 2 he says here must
refer to the things you say and the
things you do because of your medulla
Catania disini Harris Pune Jupiter
Hollow and akattak and and mahalia under
lock and key first blue Canyon
number 2 the Potter did he leave out
Carmel thinking mengapa do you know more
Torah from blackboard
dear money addict and karma profiteer
because that was already in in the
misunderstanding can I do da da da da la
casa la palma that's karma at the mind
- karma Terapeak era okay sick consumed
by daenam long chilean seeker third line
here which means says the other seven
are suffering Camus dandy periscopic at
the scene II am an attack on - jewel
idea when these things are just kind of
what are the objects in your life that
you experience don't open any highness
much of object
Tellem he too young under Alami tangle
Jin Yong Jun Jie few front back to
camera problems to a blast out done how
they happen in order and how you shut
them down became a number negative jetty
taro root and then became an animatic
America karate Daniel gamba
automatically doing a meditation on the
pain of life La Cabana Bernard and
Esther automatics plug accommodate hace
para trás a socket kahit open
and then automatically there will be a
shift in your heart tanka Modesto
Tomatis I can add a precursor and he'd
understand oh my god I'm like a prisoner
in this wheel and a cameraman at the
Edwin says petit ananda la mirada eeny
this world is a prison Sunaina de la
pinata
my life is a hit of saya adalah live
I've been inside a prison
so more hidup scepter daddy Taliban
Jarrah and I'm condemned in this prison
yes I do go bleep injera any the only
way I'd leave this prison is to die
shuttle cetera Simon Inca camp in Jeddah
in udara and it's not a metaphor it's
real Danny to buchan Roopa man-eatin
young how wealthy the epital is a
propaganda capitalist propaganda it
doesn't matter
did a masala you are still locked in the
jail of death okay animosity could GD
p-- and Jericho mafia then
a number one you'd be crazy to think
that all the people before you died but
you're not gonna die
hello noburo Sato and a concealer on to
perfect for someone or on sebelum under
Meninga that that be under did a karate
then if someone told you you know
there's a pretty easy way because I
remember tau and tau are Italian I have
to be crazy not to
lalu so epic it and opposite Kira
Chiquitita but I got a convector so just
the idea my life is like a prison no
matter what happens in my life good or
bad I will lose everything even my life
daddy honey he day he took suspended
epithelia Penta tell a bit of SIA
bye oh maybe this way I can get I mean I
don't want to die but I would like to
change life and make it like a paradise
come again again and I'm gonna plant
either in the Oval keen a doTERRA sorry
was a clue are also definitely dying in
mati to be saying in mokuba he do plan
number despedida circa sang in Morocco
canítö then he says me engineer that's
that renunciation diamond octagon yen
Julian he'd open a lot on I think in in
English the word renunciation first of
all
waiters and restaurants never used this
word term Assange grease Capitola can
dama dama playin D restaurant tidak
pernah Munakata in d even in the ancient
Christian tradition where the word came
from pecan delante de c Kristen cool
attempt at kata ito Brasa
all right it means I will stay in a
monastery I will eat simple food I will
have simple been like that in a bratty
second Engel DPR a second McCann
McCallister hunnid and second family
kita potater cetera Hannes appetito
but the word in Buddhism that the
original engine epic attitude are a
Buddhist guitarist Lee Jung Joon
it has a different feeling and a
different meaning America president
repeated and studied ACI course as you
know this is the first of the three
principal paths to surgically annoying
bludger ACI and at Alinea dalla young
for temerity cajole or uttama
and it's very simple to explain it it
just means I want to get out that's a
non-starter now 20 lasagna
Johanna bratty saya ingin no I mean what
it means in the Christian world
renunciation it doesn't mean that you
needed a family capitellum Kristin young
brat Eponine oricon the Dhamma Malika
Artie - it doesn't mean I will avoid
fancy food or I won't go on vacations i
watch movies in ET de prata secondary
mccannon mara a Tau Ceti talkin perky
bleep or Atossa Tita a comma not a
villain in Buddhism men jungmin's I
definitely wanna hear Buddhist / ninja
bratty saya pastor ingin kau artery
Sydney so your life from the time you're
born today from the minute you are born
to the minute you die Jerry hadouken de
siècle here 30 minute under de Larroque
on camera and is exactly the same as a
prison simona / system are in a Banjara
when you say this guy is rich you just
mean this guy has more money in his
prison cell that the same cell that I
mean the kinda man got Canora India and
a honey per ticket or an animal akela
people want his self injera it to sell
young sama young saya Mizuki or this
movie starts very beautiful she's in the
same prison Sheldon I mean she's gonna
lose all her beauty also debido a una
parte di dystopia young Shah Mardan
Antipas a brother dandy occur killing
and some orchids are taken a Jukka so I
don't see I don't see this word
renunciation meaning grumpy ordained
person said a table had Catapano Lacan
indeed bramara Parowan / Mara
in many religious traditions including
Manya 30c a gamma thermos of Buddhist
renunciation another the picture in your
mind camber column picker and under it's
like a monk or nun whose support DP
Arawa at the bureau at the end didn't
work yeah they're not gonna eat donuts
because they taste good ricotta karma
condone utkatasana enough yeah you don't
think of someone joyful and I detect
when we kill cancer songyang minion
Duncan
but what we talked about today
Patera Connecticut Zika and America
panna cotta it's sort of like Steve Jobs
or something you need Zapatistas water
it means you're very excited me Bharata
Anderson got person bonnet and tongue is
a fizzy burrow in England yeah yeah
maraquita mum what's broken bottle let's
make a new kind of car man I get that
man but no pigeon is but it should be
like that
yeah yeah it don't matter get a quantity
to name is Mary get a bottle a incred
yeah kabisa okay so it's kind of like I
don't know
Elon Musk doesn't want to ride around in
a car that's polluting the whole planet
okay Teddy the same items either a towel
Ellen mass data in a night won't be long
went to Murray's a little planet here's
like a positive happy Cove Asian yes but
the mammalogy feast is a non positive
Karan
yeah let's get stinky cars yeah my to
get that many clean step or a mood up a
contested and kombucha suru dunya
that's that's how renunciation should
taste
Interlaken yes I want this stupid
sighing in tune and currents entering
into neon bodeaux in it
oh shut it crippled support ammonia tua
no teeth they die I love that bug Aquila
lumati and a tau is it a correct I want
some cool Diegans are at the end okay so
get that feeling about renunciation okay
did it up I can press and on Panola can
and I don't know you could probably see
Saturday tau animal can be some recycle
arm room here membrane DC knee is
shifting Saddam precursor from
explaining the problem Dharam
intelliscan masala and you could feel
sort of this Elan Mustang then Anna be
Samaras a consummate a any hull alas
Okita Pune so Lucy and a conductor let's
get on to the solution in the next video
tell Mary Kate American so Lucy talent
video brick goodness see you then
sampai jumpa